dualshockers.com 2018-06-24

# Privacy Policy

**Miniature Version of the Privacy Policy:**

You know that DualShockers, Inc. wouldn’t do anything to hurt you guys, right? _Right?_ We wouldn’t – it’s not on our “To do” list.  DualShockers, Inc. is a trusted community site committed to protecting your privacy. What this means is that we will never _ever_ sell your email address, nor share it with anyone, spam you, or send you pictures of the DualShockers staff in monkey suits – ever. For your protection, we have a couple of goodies implemented that will keep potential bad men away. We would also never ask you for your credit card, phone, passwords, date of birth, demographic information, IP address, gender, etc. In all honesty, we could care less if you decide not to share your legal name with us – nicknames are perfectly fine and would probably be your best bet.

If you decide to become a part of the DualShockers, Inc. video game community thingy, you are only agreeing to become some virtual entity in the realm that is cyberspace to discuss video games with us. That’s basically it. Really.

**The Hefty Version of the Privacy Policy:**

DualShockers, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. The following statement details our ongoing support for the responsible collection and management of Internet user information.

**Internet User Information:**

When DualShockers, Inc. displays an advertisement on your computer, we do not collect _any_ personal identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, telephone number or email address. DualShockers, Inc. does, like other Internet advertisers, collect certain information which cannot personally identify you (Cookies! – and no, not the kind favored by the Cookie Monster; It’s the kind that is stored on your browser on your computer’s hard drive as small pieces of information). This category of information is generally referred to as non-personally-identifiable information includes information like the server or ISP (Internet Service Provider) you use, and/or type of web browser used. There are cases where you, the Internet user, may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a particular ad (a survey or purchase order form, for example). In such cases, the third party advertising with DualShockers, Inc. may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. In turn, the advertiser uses the information to respond to your request.

Additionally, DualShockers, Inc. does not confess any information regarding the users who use email for correspondence with the webmaster or any representative of DualShockers, Inc.

**Online Advertising**

DualShockers, Inc. does not sell its own ads. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including any of your information such as: your name, email address, home address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our website, other websites, and other forms of media about good and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please feel free to check out [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

To sum it up in basic terms, it’s basically cookies that say something along the lines of “Ok, you saw this advertisement already,” or “So this person clicked on a banner advertisement for mining helmets, so let’s send them some more information on them.” DualShockers, Inc. does not share any information from your personal account with advertisers.

**Learn to Abuse Common Sense with All Your Online Activity**

Even though we try our hardest to protect your information from people that have nothing else better to do than engage in malicious activities, our policy can’t always protect your online privacy and security in all circumstances. Scandalous advertisers, immoral hackers/crackers, and scam artists are constantly searching the Internet looking for some fresh meat to abuse. Your best protection against these kinds of folks is to understand the limits to privacy on the Internet and use common sense in all your online activities.

Also be aware that email can be an essentially insecure form of communication. Remember that third parties are capable of illegally intercepting your unencrypted messages, including online greetings. Anytime you visit a chat room or post a message to an online bulletin board, your email address can be accessed by advertisers looking to compile lists for unsolicited commercial email (which can also be referred to as spam).

For your own protection, be sure that you only disclose your email in circumstances which are safe to do so in. Beware of scams in which persons unknown to you request any information that they can use against you (such as your name, screen name, password, credit card information, address, etc.). Make sure that you verify the identity of anyone asking for your personal information. If you don’t know them, it’s probably best to ignore their requests. Always monitor your children’s online activities and educate them as to the rules for safe internet use. For more information, check out [http://www.getnetwise.org/](https://www.getnetwise.org/).

**Changes and Updates**

DualShockers, Inc. may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended policy on its website. The amended policy shall automatically take effect 30 days after it is first posted on the website. Continued use of the site after any changes made to this Privacy Policy signifies a visitor’s understanding, intention and agreement to be bound by such change. It is the visitor’s responsibility to monitor this Privacy Policy for changes. Any change to this Privacy Policy shall be effective as to any visitor who has visited the site before the changes were made.

This Privacy Policy is effective February 22, 2009.

**Contacting the Webmaster**

If there are any questions rummaging in your brain that you would like to ask regarding the privacy statement, the practices of DualShockers, Inc., or your dealings with this website, you can contact me at [yaris@dualshockers.com](mailto:yaris@dualshockers.com).  I promise to do the very best with responding as hastily as possible.

Copyright©2009 DualShockers, Inc. All rights reserved.
